<!--
  ~ Copyright (c) 2018  STMicroelectronics – All rights reserved
  ~ The STMicroelectronics corporate logo is a trademark of STMicroelectronics
  ~
  ~ Redistribution and use in source and binary forms, with or without modification,
  ~ are permitted provided that the following conditions are met:
  ~
  ~ - Redistributions of source code must retain the above copyright notice, this list of conditions
  ~    and the following disclaimer.
  ~
  ~ - Redistributions in binary form must reproduce the above copyright notice, this list of
  ~    conditions and the following disclaimer in the documentation and/or other materials provided
  ~    with the distribution.
  ~
  ~ - Neither the name nor trademarks of STMicroelectronics International N.V. nor any other
  ~    STMicroelectronics company nor the names of its contributors may be used to endorse or
  ~    promote products derived from this software without specific prior written permission.
  ~
  ~ - All of the icons, pictures, logos and other images that are provided with the source code
  ~    in a directory whose title begins with st_images may only be used for internal purposes and
  ~    shall not be redistributed to any third party or modified in any way.
  ~
  ~ - Any redistributions in binary form shall not include the capability to display any of the
  ~    icons, pictures, logos and other images that are provided with the source code in a directory
  ~    whose title begins with st_images.
  ~
  ~ THIS SOFTWARE IS PROVIDED BY THE COPYRIGHT HOLDERS AND CONTRIBUTORS "AS IS" AND ANY EXPRESS OR
  ~ IMPLIED WARRANTIES, INCLUDING, BUT NOT LIMITED TO, THE IMPLIED WARRANTIES OF MERCHANTABILITY
  ~ AND FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE ARE DISCLAIMED. IN NO EVENT SHALL THE COPYRIGHT HOLDER
  ~ OR CONTRIBUTORS BE LIABLE FOR ANY DIRECT, INDIRECT, INCIDENTAL, SPECIAL, EXEMPLARY, OR
  ~ CONSEQUENTIAL DAMAGES (INCLUDING, BUT NOT LIMITED TO, PROCUREMENT OF SUBSTITUTE GOODS OR
  ~ SERVICES; LOSS OF USE, DATA, OR PROFITS; OR BUSINESS INTERRUPTION) HOWEVER CAUSED AND ON ANY
  ~ THEORY OF LIABILITY, WHETHER IN CONTRACT, STRICT LIABILITY, OR TORT (INCLUDING NEGLIGENCE OR
  ~ OTHERWISE) ARISING IN ANY WAY OUT OF THE USE OF THIS SOFTWARE, EVEN IF ADVISED OF THE POSSIBILITY
  ~ OF SUCH DAMAGE.
  ~
  -->

<resources>
    <string name="Followers_Cursors">
        This is a new feature!\n
        You don\'t need to watch the screen to pilot the drone any more.\n
        In fact the cursor is redrawn and centered wherever you touch the screen.\n
        In this way the drone doesn\'t move at the first touch, it starts moving only\n
        if you move your finger around the screen.\n
        The standard cursors are fixed, so you need to watch the screen to point\n
        your finger toward the center to avoid moving the drone.\n
        Try it!\n
        You can drive the drone without watching the screen now.\n
        If your finger is too close to the bounds of screen then\n
        the application will create a feedback vibration.\n
    </string>

    <string name="SwapPlanes">
        This is a new feature!\n
        You can swap the x, y, z axis of analog pilot cursors.\n
        (x = left/right, y = altitude, z = frontward/backward)\n
        In this way you can use the right cursor to obtain a death loop\n
        and left cursor to generate arcs.\n
        It is a new way to pilot a drone.\n
        Some inputs can\'t be executed because they are not supported\n
        by the propeller motor.\n
        Try it!\n
    </string>

    <string name="HelpDescription">This Help is scrollable</string>
    <string name="SeekBar">
        You can scale the speed of the propeller motors, so you can reduce\n
        the speed for smooth flight
    </string>
    <string name="textViewBattery" translatable="false">
        The led shows you the battery level in percentage format. 4.2V is 100%
    </string>
    <string name="textViewRSSI" translatable="false">
        The led shows you the power level of the BLE drone connection in db.
    </string>
    <string name="Offset">
        The "Offset" left/right button enables you to swap between the analogic/digital cursor.\n
        By pressing the same button the cursor types are swapped.\n
        If offset is pressed, the digital cursors change the offset Yaw,\n
        pitch and roll and altitude by 1/128 of their max value for each click.
    </string>
    <string name="Take_off">
        Third Action before starting\n
        The "Take_off" button is for drone take-off.\n
        During this phase it is necessary to use the altitude cursor to stop the drone.\n
        Once the drone is flying, the same button becomes "Land" for landing.\n
    </string>
    <string name="initDrone">
        Second Action before starting\n
        The first button is for sensor calibration, so the drone gyroscpe sensor starts \n
        from the correct value, because the drone board may not be completely horizontal \n
        The Take_off button requires a 1 sec press to become active. \n
        If the button is pressed for at least 1 sec, then button becomes\n
        green for 2 sec else red for 2 sec. \n
        Use it before taking off.\n
        The second button is for arming the propeller motors.\n
        Once the drone is flying, the same button will stop the propeller motors.\n
        The Stop button is the last possible option to stop the drone\n
        when you have lost control of the drone.\n
        The third item is the led to indicate the Arming status\n
        (green is armed, red is not armed).\n
    </string>
    <string name="Connection">
        First action before starting\n
        The "Connection" button enables drone connection via BLE.\n
        After pressing, the page becomes the connection page\n
        to search and select your drone in the list.\n
        Click on your drone to connect and the page will return to the homepage.\n
        The button changes color in order to indicate the connection status:\n
        \t\t\t\tBlue light is for starting connection phase.\n
        \t\t\t\tgreen means connected.\n
        \t\t\t\tYellow means searching connection.\n
        \t\t\t\tRed means no connection.\n
    </string>
    <string name="DataDrone">
        The first selector is for enabling drone sensor data: \n
        \t\t\t\tAccelerometer\n
        \t\t\t\tGyroscope\n
        \t\t\t\tMagnetometer\n
        \t\t\t\tPressure\n
        \t\t\t\tAltitude\n
        Instead of -STDrone software version- you will see\n
        the sensor data with their metrics.\n
        The second selector is for enabling or disabling log file generation\n
        with the drone sensor data timestamp.\n
        Please be careful!!!\n
        the filenames are always different,\n
        so you need to remember to manually delete obsolete files\n
        The directory is stored in the main root of your sdcard:\n
        /STMicroelectronics/logs\n
    </string>
    <string name="YawDisable">
        The selector is to enable or disable Yaw (this type of activation is suggested for beginners)\n
    </string>
    <string name="Shape">
        The selector is for switching between the square or circle shaped cursor.\n
        The square is optimum to have the right correspondence with the drone\'s dynamics.\n
        In fact the maximum speed is at the corner of square.\n
        Before moving, you can rotate to 45 degrees in the right direction by using Yaw.\n
        Then you can try the maximum speed moving your finger to the corner of square.\n
    </string>
    <string name="Sensitivity">
        The "Sensitivity" button is for moving into the Sensitivity page\n
        to set the Sensitivity Analog Cursor\n
        The speed at which your fingers move are usually proportional\n
        to the speed rotation request for the propeller motors\n
        The Sensitivity page enables nonlinear behaviour.\n
        In particular it is possible to increase the speed slope rate\n
        when you touch the cursor for the first time.\n
        Start slope rate can be increased by setting the sensitivity seek bar value, \n
		but this is limited to the beginning only (due to inherent maximum speed limitations of motor, \n 
		which are reached at the outside limit of the circle)\n
		Hence this functionality works best around at the centre of the circle \n
    </string>
    <string name="SensitivitySeekBar">
        The seek bar changes the start slope rate of sensitivity\n
        when you press the cursor for the first time.\n
        The selectors are for Yaw, Pitch/Roll and Altitude.\n
        The value can change from 1 to the Max value.\n
        1 is to disable nonlinear behaviour, so speed rotation request\n
        is proportional to finger speed \n
        x value means x times higher than the proportional speed only for the first touch\n
        If you choose to increase start slope rate then please be aware that\n
		the speed increase will be best at the centre of the circle\n
        and that the nonlinear behaviour (i.e finger speed vs. motor speed)increases as you approach the outside of the circle\n
		causing a relative speed decrease\n
		Start slope rate can be increased by setting the sensitivity seek bar value, \n
		but this is limited to the beginning only (due to inherent maximum speed limitations of motor, \n 
		which are reached at the outside limit of the circle)\n
		Hence this functionality works best around at the centre of the circle \n

    </string>
    <string name="SensitivitySeekBarMax">
        The selector is for the change seek bar scope\n
        If -Start slope rate Max- is selected the Max range can change by seek bar\n
        There is a mininum (invariable) value\n
        Changing the maximum values, except for nonlinear disable, also start slope rate\n
        change whose value can then be seen\n
    </string>
</resources>
