<!--
  ~ Copyright (c) 2018  STMicroelectronics – All rights reserved
  ~ The STMicroelectronics corporate logo is a trademark of STMicroelectronics
  ~
  ~ Redistribution and use in source and binary forms, with or without modification,
  ~ are permitted provided that the following conditions are met:
  ~
  ~ - Redistributions of source code must retain the above copyright notice, this list of conditions
  ~    and the following disclaimer.
  ~
  ~ - Redistributions in binary form must reproduce the above copyright notice, this list of
  ~    conditions and the following disclaimer in the documentation and/or other materials provided
  ~    with the distribution.
  ~
  ~ - Neither the name nor trademarks of STMicroelectronics International N.V. nor any other
  ~    STMicroelectronics company nor the names of its contributors may be used to endorse or
  ~    promote products derived from this software without specific prior written permission.
  ~
  ~ - All of the icons, pictures, logos and other images that are provided with the source code
  ~    in a directory whose title begins with st_images may only be used for internal purposes and
  ~    shall not be redistributed to any third party or modified in any way.
  ~
  ~ - Any redistributions in binary form shall not include the capability to display any of the
  ~    icons, pictures, logos and other images that are provided with the source code in a directory
  ~    whose title begins with st_images.
  ~
  ~ THIS SOFTWARE IS PROVIDED BY THE COPYRIGHT HOLDERS AND CONTRIBUTORS "AS IS" AND ANY EXPRESS OR
  ~ IMPLIED WARRANTIES, INCLUDING, BUT NOT LIMITED TO, THE IMPLIED WARRANTIES OF MERCHANTABILITY
  ~ AND FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE ARE DISCLAIMED. IN NO EVENT SHALL THE COPYRIGHT HOLDER
  ~ OR CONTRIBUTORS BE LIABLE FOR ANY DIRECT, INDIRECT, INCIDENTAL, SPECIAL, EXEMPLARY, OR
  ~ CONSEQUENTIAL DAMAGES (INCLUDING, BUT NOT LIMITED TO, PROCUREMENT OF SUBSTITUTE GOODS OR
  ~ SERVICES; LOSS OF USE, DATA, OR PROFITS; OR BUSINESS INTERRUPTION) HOWEVER CAUSED AND ON ANY
  ~ THEORY OF LIABILITY, WHETHER IN CONTRACT, STRICT LIABILITY, OR TORT (INCLUDING NEGLIGENCE OR
  ~ OTHERWISE) ARISING IN ANY WAY OUT OF THE USE OF THIS SOFTWARE, EVEN IF ADVISED OF THE POSSIBILITY
  ~ OF SUCH DAMAGE.
  ~
  -->

<resources>
    <string name="Followers_Cursors">
        This is a new feature!\n
        You don\'t need to watch the screen to pilot the drone any more.\n
        In fact the Cursor is redrawed and centered where you put the finger into screen.\n
        In this way the drone does\'t move at the first touch, it starts moving only\n
        if you move your fingher on the screen.\n
        The standard cursors are fixed, so you need to watch the screen to point\n
        the fingher toward the center to avoid moving drone.\n
        Try it!\n
        You can drive the drone without to watch the screen now.\n
        If your fingher is to much closed to the bounds of screen then\n
        a vibration will give you a feedback.\n
    </string>

    <string name="SwapPlanes">
        This is a new feature!\n
        You can swap x, y, z axis of analog pilot cursors.\n
        (x = left/right, y = altitude, z = frontward/backward)\n
        In this way you can use right cursor to obtain death loop\n
        and left cursor to generate arcs.\n
        It is a new way to pilot drone.\n
        Some input can\'t be executed because are out of range\n
        of propoller motors possibilities.\n
        Try it!\n
    </string>

    <string name="HelpDescription">This Help is scrollable</string>
    <string name="SeekBar">
        You can scale the speed of propoller motors, so you can reduce\n
        the speed for a smooth driving
    </string>
    <string name="textViewBattery" translatable="false">
        The led shows you the percentage of battery level. 4.2V is 100%
    </string>
    <string name="textViewRSSI" translatable="false">
        The led shows you the power level of BLE drone connection in db.
    </string>
    <string name="Offset">
        The Offset left/right button allows to swap analogic/digital cursor.\n
        Pressing the same button the cursors types are swapped.\n
        If offeset is pressed, then digital cursors changes the offset Yaw,\n
        pitch and roll and altitude by 1/128 of their max value for each click.
    </string>
    <string name="Take_off">
        Third Action before starts\n
        The Take_off button is for taking off the drone.\n
        During this phase is necessary to use altitude cursor to stop the drone.\n
        When drone flies, the same button become a Land for landing.\n
    </string>
    <string name="initDrone">
        Second Action before starts\n
        The first Button is for sensor calibration, so drone Gyroscpe sensor starts \n
        from correct value, because the drone board could be a bit not horizontal \n
        The Take_off button requires 1 sec pressed to be active. \n
        If button is pressed for at least 1 sec, then button becomes\n
        green for 2 sec else red for 2 sec. \n
        Use it before to take off.\n
        The second button is for Arming the propoller motors.\n
        When drone flies, the same button become a stop propoller motors.\n
        Stop button is the last possible action to stop drone\n
        when you don't have any more the drone control.\n
        The third item is the led to know Arming status\n
        (green is armed, red is not armed).\n
    </string>
    <string name="Connection">
        First Action before starts\n
        Connection Button allows to connect the drone by BLE.\n
        After pressing, the page becomes the connection page\n
        to search and select your drone into the list.\n
        Click on your drone to allow connection and the page return the home one.\n
        The button changes color in order to the status connection:\n
        \t\t\t\tBlue light is for starting connection phase.\n
        \t\t\t\tgreen means connected.\n
        \t\t\t\tYellow means searching connection.\n
        \t\t\t\tRed means no connection.\n
    </string>
    <string name="DataDrone">
        The first selector is for enabling drone sensor data: \n
        \t\t\t\tAccelerometer\n
        \t\t\t\tGyroscope\n
        \t\t\t\tMagnetometer\n
        \t\t\t\tPressure\n
        \t\t\t\tAltitude\n
        Instead of -STDrone software version- will be visualized\n
        these sensor data with their measure unit.\n
        The second selector is for Enable or disable Logging File\n
        with timestamp of drone sensor data.\n
        Pay Attention!!!\n
        the name of files are always different,\n
        so you remeber to delete manually useless file\n
        The directory is into main root of sdcard:\n
        /STMicroelectronics/logs\n
    </string>
    <string name="YawDisable">
        The selector is for enable or disable Yaw (activation suggested for beginners)\n
    </string>
    <string name="Shape">
        The selector is for changing square or circle shape cursor.\n
        The Square is optimum to have the right corrispondence with drone dynamic.\n
        In fact the maximum speed is on the corner of square.\n
        Before moving, you can rotate to 45degree into right direction by using Yaw.\n
        Then you try the maximum speed moving fingher on the corner of square.\n
    </string>
    <string name="Sensitivity">
        Sensitivity button is for moving into Sensitivity page\n
        to set Sensitivity Analog Cursor\n
        The speed moving of finghers are usually proportionally\n
        to the speed rotation request for propoller motors\n
        The Sensitivity page allows to introduce a non linear behaviour.\n
        In particular is possible to increase the speed slope rate\n
        when you touch cursor for the first time.\n
        If you increase start slope rate then you also decrease the it\n
        when you are closed to the cursor bounds.\n
    </string>
    <string name="SensitivitySeekBar">
        The seek bar changes the start slope rate of sensitivity\n
        when you press cursor for first touch.\n
        The selector are for Yaw, Pitch/Roll and Altitude.\n
        The value can change since 1 to Max value.\n
        1 means non linear disable, so speed rotation request\n
        is proportional to speed finghers\n
        x value means x times higher than proportional speed only for first touch\n
        If you increase start slope rate then you also decrease the it\n
        when you are closed to the cursor bounds.\n
    </string>
    <string name="SensitivitySeekBarMax">
        The selector is for change seek bar scope\n
        If -Start slope rate Max- is selected the Max range can change by seek bar\n
        There is a mininum value possible not changeble\n
        Changing Max changes, except for non linear disable, also start slope rate\n
        change and its value is also visualised\n
    </string>
</resources>
